You have a serious addiction.
Yes, prophet.
With this internet.
It has become an addiction to you.
Yes, prophet.
And there is one that even sent a naked picture.
Yes, prophet it's true.
And your naked picture is there with him
You are a beautiful girl, why should you go into that?
Now you don't have affection again
It's true man of God
Good morning, Church!
If you know today is a day of your deliverance shout "Emmanuel!"
Emmanuel!!
My name is Erica Jimmy and I came from Tanzania.
And my testimony goes like this,
Last week Sunday, I received a prophecy from the man of God, Prophet TB Joshua
First he said that I'm addicted to the internet.
Then the second one he said that someone sent a naked picture to me
and me too, I sent a naked picture to him.
Then the last one he said I don't have affection for anyone
and I confess the prophecy to be 100% true.
It all started when I was 15 years old.
I started watching pornography.
I used to watch pornography just like a normal issue
just like I'm watching movies -
just as a normal issue, as a normal life.
I used to see it as a normal life.
I didn't know that it was something that was be bad;
it was like a normal life.
This issue of pornography later caused bad results.
After watching pornography I would find myself masturbating.
After masturbating I would feel like - why have I done this, why should I do this?
But I couldn't stop, I couldn't stop there.
I started developing this issue of chatting on the internet and
Facebooking a lot.
I can Facebook until the morning to sometimes 3:00 am or 4:00 am.
Can you explain to us how this addiction of pornography and chatting on the internet
has affected your life - your academics, your social life?
It affected me so much, so much
to the extent I suffered serious disappointment.
I suffered rejection, isolation and even depression.
It came to a time that I used to smoke;
I used to drink this hard alcohol.
I used to get irritated a lot.
.so easily, just little things and I could be irritated.
I could be so irritated that I could not control myself.
Then my prayer life, my prayer life just went off
I couldn't pray anymore, I couldn't read the Bible anymore.
I was just living like someone who would be living but I couldn't do anything.
The issue of pornography led me to have this kind of dreams, bad dreams.
There are times I used to see mermaids; she would come wearing this black thing on the bottom
and red beads on her neck.
She would tell me that until I bowed down to worship them,
I would never have peace of mind and they would make sure I would die.
It came about that I met this man last year, in my country Tanzania.
We engaged ourselves in a relationship.
Then he travelled to Europe.
We were chatting and then came a time he asked me to send him my naked picture
but I refused at first and then he sent his own.
He was saying like, "I did it for you, so you have to do it for me".
Then I did it for him.
When this man sent me his naked picture, he asked me to send him my naked pictures -
of maybe my breast or private part.
Then he would come with these strong, romantic words like,
'Baby, you know I am horny. Could you touch this part, could you do this?'
So at the end I found myself masturbating.
So these were the trauma you were going through
and after all these issues you were talking about can you tell us
what were the issues, the problems that you usually encountered daily as you did all this?
Disappointment, rejection, isolation, depression
and I used to isolate myself; sometimes I didn't want to stay close to people.
Sometimes, I didn't want to stay close to my family.
I would just isolate myself, somewhere far.
What you are talking about, did you at one point share with your family members?
No it's a shameful thing I couldn't share with anyone - even with a close friend.
Even someone I could share my bed with - I could not tell anyone.I kept it all to myself.
So most of the things you are sharing with us today, your parents are hearing for the first time?
I believe they are shaking right now wherever they are, I know they are watching Emmanuel TV.
Yes, we know your parents will be very happy today that you are delivered from all this.
Tell us, at one point in time in your life you were experiencing bad dreams?
Can you tell us also how those bad dreams affected you in the physical?
It affected me so much. At a time I dreamt that I was in a hospital bed, lying down there
helpless with no one to help me
Then when I turned to the other side of the bed I saw a lion - a very big one with a long tail and human head.
Then he said to me "Erica, this time around we will catch you; you will never go ahead of us!"
So after I woke up, I told my mom about that dream.
Then my mum introduced me to Emmanuel TV.
Along the line, later we had this journey with my brother.
My brother prayed by himself in his room; he anointed the car and himself with a Morning Water.
You mean you were travelling together with your brother?
Yes, I was travelling together with my brother.
So he anointed the car, he anointed himself before he we traveled.
But I didn't pray; I just woke up, entered the car and we just went!
Along the line I fell asleep
Then the voice came to me: "Erica, wake up and pray"
I woke up and asked my brother, "Were you talking to me?"
He said: "No, I was not talking to you."
Then I fell asleep again.
The voice came again, very humble, "Erica, wake up and pray.
But still I could not pray although I did wake up.
I could not pray; I was just amazed wondering if it was a voice or I was just dreaming.
Then the voice came the third time, "Erica, wake up and pray!"
Now, it was very strong - 'Wake up and pray!'
But still, I woke up but could not pray
And I then saw the car in the bush!
So that is the only thing I can remember; I could not remember anything else.
So this one is a result of that accident [pointing towards picture]
So you mean you managed to survive the accident by the Grace of God
through the medium of the Morning Water which your brother had ministered before you traveled?
Yes, it's only by the grace of God that today I'm alive, so I just say - thank You, Jesus!
And finally you came to The SCOAN?
Yes, I finally came to The Synagogue Church of all Nation to seek help.
I came for this issue of disappointment and limitation in progress.
I never knew when the man of God said: "Come!"
I never had this in my mind that he would tell me something like this.
I never knew I was the one, that I was the cause of my problem.
I never knew that. You know, I was maybe thinking he would say I had a generational curse or
that there was something that happened somewhere which was the cause of what I was going through.
But I never knew he would speak something like this - addiction to the internet because I never told anyone!
That was between me and God because I had tried to fast and pray
but I just said: "I leave it for God; one day, I will be delivered!"
And finally what happened after the man of God gave you the word of prophecy
It's the grace of God! Last week, the man of God located me; I was sitting right there.
Then the man of God was giving prophecies to the people.
Then he said that he will just prophesy for few people
But among those few people I was there.
The he said to me, Just the way you watched.
And he prayed for me, As soon as he prayed for me it was like some thing just left me off.
Something, and I felt so light, my mind became so free
my heart became so free,
then I came to know that I don't have this addiction anymore
Chatting, thinking of pornography, masturbating
You mean you are completely free
Yes, I'm completely free
Shall we put our hands together wonderfully for our Lord Jesus
You mentioned about several things that you were once addicted to,
You talked about depression that led to your smoking and drinking and you were talking about a lot of things you were into
Can you explain to us, after your deliverance, what are the things that you are longer doing anymore, after your deliverance.
The first thing I noticed after my deliverance was that I was so addicted to my phone . I could chat
The I found out that I don,t want to touch my phone so many times
Even my sisters and my brothers sent me a text and it was just yesterday I replied just one text
just like I'm fine where I am, Yes
So, does it mean you are no longer having depression, no longer feeling sad?
Yes, I don't have that depression anymore, I don't have that urge of watching pornography
I don't have that urge of masturbating, I'm free, I'm free
From smoking and drinking?
Yes, from smoking and from drinking also.
hallelujah
Shall we put our hands again for our Lord Jesus!
Yes, you mentioned that the moment man of God gave you a prophecy you realised the root cause of your problem
You identified your problem from that very moment you received your deliverance
Can you give a word of advice to those youth like you who have similar problem,
that God Almighty has just delivered you from.
Can you give them a word of advice,
To the youth - I'm starting with a youth -
I will speak both - Swahili and English
Am starting with English
To the youth - youth, you need to discover yourself
You need to discover your weakness before pointing a finger on something
You have to discover something you are addicted to
Don't point a finger to anyone, like is a cause of it, no!!
You need to discover yourself, you need to discover your weakness
Then you need to seek God for deliverance
And you say you want to advice in Swahili -
Now I will speak in Swahili -
vijana wenzangu, popote mlipo najua mnanitazama sasa hivi (my fellow youth, wherever you are I know you are watching me)
popote mlipo usione aibu kwa udhaifu uliyo nayo (where ever you are don't be ashamed for your weakness)
Mungu analeta nguvu katika madhaifu yetu. (God brings strength in our weaknesses )
Usione aibu kuleta madhaifu yako mbele za mungu (Do not be ashamed to bring your weakness before Gods strength)
atakusaidia, atakuokoa na utakua free (He will help you, he will save you and you will be free)
kwenye matatizo yako yote (from all your difficulties)
We thank God
Shall we put our hands together wonderfully for our Lord Jesus!
Just as the man of god said - when you identify your weakness, it's a victory itself, it's a half job done already
Because at that point in time Jesus will come to bring ouselves into balance
and that is what just happened to your life - the moment you discovered and aknowledged your weakness
you realised the problem is not just a generational curse
you are the root cause, the architect of your own problem and the same time Jesus has used man of God
to deliver you from the spirit of pornography and an addiction and today you can stand in the midst of children of God
to say - "thank You Jesus" - for what He has done in your life
and we believe that the Lord who has done it in your life will do it also for everyone who is facing the same challenges
you have been just delivered from, in Jesus name -
Amen.
Now, can you advise the parents
Parents, parents out there, parents here in the auditorium
Watch your children, the company they keep
watch your children, the company they keep.
You may raise your children in a good manner,
You may raise your children in a Christianity dorm.
But watch out, once they are outside, the company they keep. That's what I can advise.
We thank God for the advice you have Given and we believe that everyone who is listening you is taking your advice to heart.
Because experience is the best teacher, you just came out of this unpleasant situation
and just advice you are giving them that everyone should be able to pray for their children and watch over them
and be careful the kind of friends that they keep, they must be careful about those friends because the man of God
The only person that can take us out of the will of God is ourselves.
Therefore it imply that we must choose our freinds with care so that we may not become whom they are.
Thank you very much sister for this wonderful advice that you have given to views all over the word
Those who are watching you at this time
We thank God for your life, and we want to advice you that now that God almighty has restored you , your must realize.
and remember you are delivered for the glory of God. You must continue to make his life the standard for your life
Sorry before you go, can you explain the pictures that he wave on the board ?
the pictures you have there, can you explain to us?
This pictures, the one you see here is the day of accident
You know the car somersaulted like 10 times before it land
and here it is me 21 days after the accident, they were removing the stitches. and I still have this [shows]
So this is the scare that you sustained from the accident
yes
But today everyone is alive by the grace of God after you ministered the morning water
Yes
We thank God for your life, and we know that this is also were as a result of the life that you are coming from
You are indeed coming from unrighteousness and today our lord Jesus has pt a stop on your past
and give birth to your new future
Don't forget that as you go continue to honor Christ and continue to receive instructions from him we pray
that God almighty in his infinite mercy will give you the grace to maintain your deliverance in Jesus name